

### Contact

# Phone

(+62)881 3112 407

### **Email**

mbagusrizky15@gmail.com

#### **Address**

Jln. Nangka no.27 Sleman Yogyakarta

### Education

#### AMIKOM UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Informatics 2019 - present Semester 6th

• GPA 3.83 max 4.00

#### **SMAN 1 BANJAR**

Science 2015 - 2018

# Mohamad Bagus **Rizky**

### **Profile**

I am sixth semester Bachelor of informatics in Amikom University. I'm very passionate in programming and graphic design. I'm an energetic programmer skilled in Android Java and User Interface Design. i have experience in this division, but i looking forward to challenge myself and grow in the future. I like to learn something in my life, especially in programming and graphic design.

# **Work Experience**

### CTO in PT Karya Ahli Gizi Indonesia

July 2021 - present

Developing the company's strategy for using technological resources. Ensuring technologies are used efficiently, profitably and securely. Evaluating and implementing new systems and infrastructure.

#### LAB ASSISTANT in Amikom University

- Data Structure, 2022 present
- User Interface and User Experience, 2021-2022
- Data Stucture, 2021
- Hadware Software, 2021
- Graphic Design, 2021
- Algorithm and Programming Language, 2020

Prepare lab equipment for the upcoming practicum. Clean and maintain laboratory equipment. Assist students in doing practicum.

### • GRAPHIC DESIGNER in Al Azhar English Academy

April 2019 - Desember 2021

Conceptualizing visuals based on requirements. Creating images and layouts by hand or using design software. Testing graphics across various media.

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER in harapanrakyat.com

Desember 2020

Conceptualizing visuals based on requirements. Creating images and layouts by hand or using design software. Testing graphics across various media.

# Language

- Indonesian
- English

### Skills

- UI Design
- Graphic Design
- Programming

# Organizational Experience

### Public Relations in Multimedia Community of Amikom University

December 2021 - January 2022

Planning strategy and publicity campaign.

Write and produce presentations and press releases.

Handle inquiries from the public, the press and related organizations.

Arrange and attend invitations from other organizations

### Head of Rohis SMAN 1 Banjar

2016 - 2017

Leading and representing the routine activities of Islamic Spirituality.

Organizing and Leading Rohis meetings.

Supervise overall Rohis management activities.

Define Rohis policies in general terms.

### Head of Student Council SMPN 1 Lakbok

2013 - 2014

Lead the organization well and wisely.

Coordinate all management meetings.

Establish policies that have been prepared and planned by

the management meeting.

Lead the meeting.

Establish policies and make decisions based on deliberation and consensus.

#### **Head Scout SMPN 1 Lakbok**

2013 - 2014

Maintain and maintain solidarity among members of the Front Group.

Regulate the division of labor for the Board of Raising Officers.

Reprimand and sanction undisciplined troop members.

Set an example in all things.

# **Speakers**

Mentor Training UI/UX "Redesign Apps" by Multimedia Community Amikom University

2020

Startup Clinic "Peran UI/UX dalam Startup" by ABP Incubator x RBTV 2021

## **Social Media**











**SCAN FOR MORE**